

PROFILE

I would like to contribute to your organization as a full-stack web developer, leveraging my ability to develop E-commerce web applications using readily available web frameworks. With my passion for learning, I will be able to take part in empowering your team with my newly found coding expertise. With passion and determination, I can do what I want. There is nothing impossible.

CONTACT

PHONE: 09175481025 09202828684

WEBSITE: Website goes here

calma.shairamarie@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Taekwondo Study other language

SHAIRA MARIE D.CALMA

EDUCATION

St James Academy 2005 - 2010 -Athlete of the Year

University of the East -Caloocan

Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering
2010 – 2016
5th Year Undergraduate

Tuitt Coding Boot camp

480 Hours intensive THREE MONTHS Programming COURSE

Web And Mobile

Crash Course web and Mobile Application May 18 and May 25

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sitel - Customer Representative

2015-2016

Accepting to call to assist customer about their delivery Issue. -TOP Agent month of December 2015

Sheila Mae's Lechon Manok – Family Business

2016 - 2019

Manage our Family Business

Teletech - Customer Representative

2018-2019

Food delivery services. To assist the concern of the consumer/ dasher (who delivery the food) what happen in their order /their delivery.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootsrap
- Php
- JAVA Script
- Ajax
- Laravel
- My SQL
- Quasar

Shaira	Marie	Calma
JIIGIIG	MIGHE	Callina